http://www.greenapplebooks.com/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
Main menuShelter In Place Recs
eGift Code
HomeShop for BooksGifts and SubscriptionsEventsAbout UsSell Us Your BooksUsed and Consignment
HomeAbout UsLocations & DirectionsOur StoryWhy Green Apple?Our NewsletterEventsEvent CalendarFundraisingHolding Events at GABShop for BooksBook of the MonthNew Books We LikeRecent BestsellersSigned BooksBook Recs by SubjectRecent Award Winners2020 Booker Prize Winner2020 National Book AwardsNYTimes 10 Best Books of 20202020 National Book Critics Circle Award2020 Pen America Literary Awards2020 Whiting Award WinnersKids and TeensStaff FavoritesPre-Order BooksBIG Books (That Are Worth the Time)Anti-Racist Reading ListsAudiobooksBulk OrdersUsed BooksEbooksUHS Spring ReadingGifts & SubscriptionsGift CardseGift CardPackage DealsApple-a-Month ClubGreen Apple Shirts & MoreGreen Apple Tote BagsGreen Apple Zoom BackgroundsShop For DistractionsActivity BooksArt SuppliesColoring BooksCrosswords and SudokuGamesPuzzlesTeacher Thank You GiftSell Us Your BooksUsed/ConsignmentConsignment at Green AppleUsed Books
Search form
Search
Privacy Policy
Green Apple Books, The American Booksellers Association (“ABA”), and IndieBound.org are committed to maintaining and protecting the privacy of your personal information. The following discloses our policy for gathering and disseminating personal information collected by Green Apple Books. If you have any questions about your rights as a user of our services, you may contact Pete Mulvihill at pete@greenapplebooks.com.
This privacy policy contains information about our commitment to your privacy, including:
The information we collect and how we use it;
Your right to access or update your personally identifiable information;
Your right to opt-out of receiving communications from us; and
Our pledge to have reasonable security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse, or alteration of information under our control.
Note: This privacy policy applies to (i) personal information collected on www.greenapplebooks.com (the “Site”): and (ii) personal information collected offline or through other sources, unless otherwise noted.
A. Information We Collect
We may collect two types of information about you when you visit the Site, contact us, place an order, or in any other communication we may have with you: personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card number) and, via the Site only, non-personal, aggregate information (such as information regarding the pages on our site you have visited and your IP address).
1. Personally Identifiable Information
The only personally identifying information that we collect and store about you is the information that you have chosen to provide to us. For example, if you place an order with us, we may collect your name, mailing address, and credit card information. IN the alternative, if you register on the Site, we may collect your name, store name, your address, store address, e-mail address and other personal information so that we can process your registration. In addition, if you contact us via phone or send us e-mail requesting information about us or otherwise ask us a question, we may collect your name, phone number, address, e-mail address and other personal information so that we can respond to your request or question. We may also from time to time send you e-mail and postal correspondence regarding products and services that we believe may be of interest to you.
2. Non-Personally Identifiable Information
From the Site, we may collect and use non-personally identifiable information about you in the following ways:
Your Internet Protocol (IP) address or the proxy address of your Internet Service Provider (e.g. AOL, CompuServe, Comcast, etc.);
The resource on our server accessed as a result of the request, such as the web page, image, etc.;
The query in the request;
The name and version of your web browser;
The content of any sent or received cookie, as defined below;
The Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) that was accessed before making the request for our web server.
a. Cookies
Some parts of this Site web site may use a “cookie” – a file placed on your computer hard drive allowing our server to log the pages accessed in the Site to determine if you have visited before. This cookie captures no personally identifying information. You may set your browser to warn you when placement of a cookie is requested, and decide whether or not to accept it. Please note that by rejecting a cookie some of the features available on the site may not function properly.
b. Referrers, IP Addresses and Environmental Variables
We may also collect information through “referrers,” IP addresses and various environmental variables. A "referrer" is information the web browser passes along to the ABA web server that references the URL from which you came. An “IP Address” is a number used by computers on a network to identify your computer so that data can be transmitted to you. An “environmental variable” may include, among other things, the domain from which you access the Internet, the time you accessed the web site, the type of web browser and operating system or platform used, the Internet address or the web site you left to visit the web site, the pages you visit while at the web site and the Internet address of the web site you then visit. We may collect IP address information in order to administer the web site and to gather broad demographic information.
B. Sharing Your Information with Third Parties
1. Disclosure of Information by Us
We may share your personally identifiable information with any affiliates, partners, agents or other parties whose products and services may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to share your information in this manner, please see the "CHOICE" section below. We also reserve the right to disclose your personal and non-personal information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law; to protect our self or to protect the rights of another user; to reduce the risk of credit or other kind of fraud; or to comply with a court order.
We may also share your personally and non-personally identifiable information with third parties that help manage our web site, databases, credit card processing companies, and affiliate relationships.
We may share your information with third parties in order to fulfill your request or otherwise complete a service provided to you.
In the unlikely event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, your personally identifiable information may be transferred to this acquiring entity.
Though we may also from time to time share your personal information with third parties for research and development purposes, we will not sell your personal information to any third parties, other than as specifically disclosed in this policy.
2. Online Blogs and Forums
Our Site also may offer blogs, chatrooms and forums that allow you to post information for other users to read. You may publish information on electronic bulletin boards generally accessible to other Site subscribers. We do not assume any responsibility for the privacy or security of any such communications, and you assume all risks of publishing such information on the system for examination by others, including our employees and persons who gain unauthorized access to the site (“hackers”). Furthermore, any such information published by you will pass through and be stored upon one or more of our servers. We will access the information stored on our server(s) for three purposes: first, to verify that the Site program and system is operating properly; second, to police the content of publications in response to any customer complaints about inappropriate content, and, third, to gather information for statistical purposes. No information published by a user is to be considered an expression of opinion or fact by us. We do not adopt, ratify, guarantee or endorse the contents or accuracy of any such publications. If you believe a communication published through such a forum or blog violates your privacy, you may report the same to us by e-mailing us for investigation.
C. Third Party Links
The Site may contain links to other web sites. Additionally, third party sites may from time to time link to the Site. PLEASE BE AWARE THAT WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONTENT OR PRACTICES OF ANY OTHER SITES. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit. Our privacy policy applies solely to this Site.
D. Choice
We provide you with the following choices regarding the use of your personal information:
You may choose not to provide us with any personal information;
If you are a user of the Site, you may set your browser not to accept cookies, or to warn you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. If you choose not to accept cookies, however, your ability to navigate this web site may be hindered;
If you would like to unsubscribe to any of our services or would like us to remove you from any of our on-line mailing lists, please email us with the subject heading "unsubscribe from Green Apple Books information" or call us at 415-387-2272;
If you do not want us to share your information, please send e-mail or call us at 415-387-2272.
E. Security
We make every effort to have reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under our control, including using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to collect and transmit your information.
If you have any questions about the security of our web site, please contact Pete Mulvihill, Green Apple Books, 506 Clement Street, San Francisco, CA 94118.
F. Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our privacy policy so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of e-mail if you provided us your email address or by posting notice on our website if we do not have your e-mail address.You will then have a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
G. Special Policy Regarding Information from Children Under Thirteen Years of Age
We are not targeted to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any child under the age of 13 without parental consent. When we receive such information, we delete it as soon as we discover it and do not use it or share it with third parties.
Effective December 2013
0
My Account
login • new account • logout
forgot my password
Subscribe to our mailing list
Donate Now
Upcoming Events
Virtual Event: Megan Wagner Lloyd and Michelle Mee Nutter with Raina Telgemeier
03/02/2021 - 5:00pm
Virtual Event: Rebecca Handler
03/09/2021 - 6:00pm
more
Looking for a used book? We have tens of thousands. Call the store at 415.387.2272 and we'll check the shelves for you.
